// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions2 = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "Examples of company-side applications called … include order processing systems, payroll systems, and company communications networks",
        answer: "Enterprise applications",
        options: [
            "Enterprise applications",
            "Network operating systems NOS",
            "Operating apps",
            "Legacy systems"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "… controls the flow of data, provides data security, and manages network operations",
        answer: "System software",
        options: [
            "Enterprise software",
            "System software",
            "Application software",
            "Legacy software"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: ".…is a system dev technique that produces a graphical representation of a concept or process that systems developers can analyze, test, and modify ",
        answer: "Modeling",
        options: [
            "Prototyping",
            "Rapid app dev",
            "Scum",
            "Modeling"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "… is a system dev technique that tests system concepts and provides an opportunity to examine input, output, and user interface before final decisions are made",
        answer: "Prototyping",
        options: [
            "Prototyping",
            "Rapid app dev",
            "Scum",
            "Modeling"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which is not true for SA?",
        answer: "Sponsors",
        options: [
            "Create value for an organization",
            "Encable the organization to perform work better",
            "Do things and challenge the current way that an org works",
            "Sponsors"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Anh is working on “How will this system work.” What SDLC phase?",
        answer: "Design",
        options: [
            "Planning",
            "Analysis",
            "Implementation",
            "Design"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Willy is calculating whether a system will lower costs or increase revenues. What SDLC?",
        answer: "Planning",
        options: [
            "Analysis",
            "Design",
            "Implementation",
            "Planning"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Kemp is dealing 1-on-1 with users and business managers (including some that have little experience with tech). He is demonstrating what SA skill?",
        answer: "Interpersonal",
        options: [
            "Business",
            "Interpersonal",
            "Ethical",
            "Analytical"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Minji is a SA for Laswell Consulting. She is attending a three-day intensive workshop on developing apps in php. What skill?",
        answer: "Technical",
        options: [
            "Business",
            "Personal",
            "Analytical",
            "Technical"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Strategic planing starts with a _____ that reflects a firm's vision, purpose, and values",
        answer: "Mission statement",
        options: [
            "Relationshipn diagram",
            "Feasibility study",
            "Performance assessment",
            "Mission statement"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Of the measures of feasibility, questions such as “Does management support the project?” and “Will the new system require training for users?” would help predict a system’s _______.",
        answer: "Operational feasibility",
        options: [
            "Schedule feasibility",
            "Technical feasibility ",
            "Economic feasibility",
            "Operational feasibility"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Projects where management has a choice in implementing them are called __________ projects.",
        answer: "Discretionary",
        options: [
            "Discretionarys",
            "Nondiscretionaryr",
            "Appended",
            "Concatenated"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Identify a typical example of a system requirement for the performance category",
        answer: "The student records system must produce class lists within five hours after the end of registration",
        options: [
            "The purchasing system must provide suppliers with up-to-date specifications",
            "Each input form must include date, time, product code, customer number, and quantity",
            "The manager of the sales department must approve orders that exceed a customers credit limit",
            "The student records system must produce class lists within five hours after the end of registration"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Which of the following is an example of a discretionary project?",
        answer: "Creating a new report for a user",
        options: [
            "Creating a new report for a user",
            "Adding a report required by a new federal law",
            "Including annual updates to payroll and tax percentages",
            "Updating quarterly changes in reporting requirements for an insurance processing system"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Which of the following is a typical example of a system requirement for the process category?",
        answer: "The equipment rental system must not execute new rental transactions for customers who have overdue accountst",
        options: [
            "The website must report online volume statistics every four hours and hourly during peak periods",
            "The system must be operated seven days a week, 365 days a year",
            "The equipment rental system must not execute new rental transactions for customers who have overdue accountst",
            "All transactions must have audit trails "
        ]
    },


];